I am not going to make any fun of religion.
Religion is very beautiful.  All the religions are
equally beautiful.  One is a little better.   The
rest of
your religion is like that of your father.
You get it as soon as you are born.  You do
n't ask him any questions.  You
accept it as it is and are unable to hear anything against it.
Someone else's religion is like that
of an uncle.  Sam is just like your father.
But you think he will take over our house.
[Applause]
[Music]
Modi ji inspires me.  I
want to work with him.  I
want to be his personal photographer.
I know everything about Modi ji,
from which angle his photos look good.   Do you
know from which angle Modi ji's photos
look good?  From every angle.  Rudeness will not be
tolerated here.  [Laughter] Modi ji goes and
takes a photographer with him,
what a chill job he has.  He travels the whole world.
He had just gone to Italy.
He had just gone to Italy.  Some friend of
his lives there.  [laughter] I had
said that I had got you and I also posted those photos. What beautiful
photos they were. Modi is standing in the balcony of a building.
[sound of clearing throat] Ji and
Bhabhi ji are
standing in the balcony of the building. The first
photo is chill, couple goals, good. In the second photo,
in a building in Rome city of Italy,
Modi ji is showing something to Meloni.
[sound of clearing throat]
[laughter]
Clicking the photo,
and Meloni is saying, I live here.
[laughter]
That's the building.
We have a building there too.  [laughs]
In the next photo, I am showing something to Modi ji, saying, look at the
bridge.   He
says he is also here.  This one does
n't fall off.
[applause]
In the next photo we [laughs] Nice.  I like
him.
Ok.  Have any of you been abroad?   From
abroad Modi ji.  [laughter]
Nice.  You have boar hair in your backyard too.
[Applause]
Just Raise Your Hands who have gone to whatever country.   I
want to tell those who have not gone that
I have gone.
[laughter]
When you go to a first-all country,
Europe, Australia, Canada, America.  Come back to
India.  You get a reality check.
You become a little critical.
This is your first thought.  Like you
land at the airport and come out.  The first thought is
whether we are
living the life of insects.  Right?  First thought: Are
these Europeans living like insects?   Have
you seen insects?
Imagine there are a lot of insects.
Now in your imagination those insects are
driving in many lanes.
[laughter] Did
an ant in Imagination overtake you like that
?
These are insects.  They have no status.
We are [ __ ] lions.  [Laughter] You see, the lion keeps
running around here like a clown.   I
urinated wherever I wanted.  He caught whoever he wanted and
ate them.  [laughter] He's
licking his balls.   Have you
ever seen a lion kill a deer, eat it and
throw whatever was left in the dustbin?  [laughter] The
lion is upper caste.  The lion does not do all this.
Lion,
we are lions brother.  Lion.  People say that
Indians do not have civic sense.
Europeans don't have an anus in their ass.
[laughter]
That he should do something.  They have no status in
front of us.  They call themselves democracies.
They do not have basic rights.  Like
you're driving in Europe.  You
gave the right indicator.  The vehicle behind
gets the signal from the right indicator.  I
think this has to go right.  [laughter]
Then you know what he does?  He lets it go.
Loser.  [laughter]
Now drive here.  You gave the right indicator.  The
vehicle coming behind
gets the signal.  Right indicator.   Go right and
see.
[laughs] I have to go
right, the rest will be left, it comes suddenly, suddenly once
I gave the right indicator,
a biker came and uprooted my indicator and
took it away [laughs]
it is fixed in the rear view mirror [laughs]
but he did not run away, he was a lion,
he stopped the bike and said to me, hey that
blind idiot
[prasadha] I am
blind as well.
When something like this happens, the rest of the people stop their vehicles.
He said, brother, you have been insulted.  Do
you have any comebacks?  [laughter] I
said this is how to fight.  There is no comeback.
I said I am thinking.  After 10 minutes
I said, are you deaf?  [laughter]
He says it himself, you won, man.
This was great.  Not very basic rights.
He can't do anything.  You're driving in Europe.
You overtook someone.  Do you
know what happens after that?   Nothing happens.
One should have some capability to do something.
They have no status at all.  Now drive here.
You overtook someone.  Then you know
what happens?  Then the race begins.
[laughter] Race.  I once
overtook a man in Gurgaon.  He raced till Goa.
[laughter] He
arrived before me.  He tells me
I won.  [laughter]
[sound of throat clearing] I had to
come here, you idiot.  [laughter]
Guess who won once.   Do you
understand?  When I was driving,
I was thinking that I am such a fool to be going to
Goa by car.  No
one else would do this except me.  This one
arrived just to prove it.  He
[sound of clearing throat] stayed with me at the dhaba.
I was observing him.
[laughter] He's
eating it quickly.
Bhai sahab, the countdown race is going on, friend
[laughter] it seems like a joke to you that there is a race going on,
who told you this, it came to me, Bhai
sahab, are you having a race [laughter] am
I having a race
[sound of clearing throat] I do
n't know, most of the rivalries are one sided
in our country, one person is putting in all his efforts to
win, the
other person has no idea
that he is in the game, the same is the scene of Modi ji and Rahul
Gandhi, if
any accident happens abroad then tell me
what do you do?  These people immediately
call an ambulance [laughs]
They don't even feel ashamed that someone has had an
accident and they make fun of it.  No, go to the
hospital immediately if an accident happens here.  You have
seen 100 people gather.  They
form a circle and stand around it.  Even if an
ambulance is passing by, it may
not be visible.  [laughter]
And let's make circles.  Don't pay attention to him.  They
start talking to each other.
True Story: A man was going in front of me on a bike.
Suddenly a cow appeared in front of him.
No, it was not a cow.
[Applause] There
was no cow.   There was
n't a cow [laughs].  She was a buffalo.   It was
white in colour and suddenly
a buffalo of maroon colour came in front of it and
its balance got disturbed
and it kept rubbing for about 100 metres and hit
a pole and fell down.
Immediately 100 people reached there and formed a circle.
I also felt like it and entered that circle.
As soon as I entered, a man was standing there. I
asked him what happened. He says the youth pack is
rotten and useless.
I said brother
[laughs]
put your hand on your heart and tell me one thing.  Are you
from Punjab?  [laughs] He
says yes, he is from Punjab.  Where are you from in Punjab
?  Kapurthala says.  I asked where Kapurthala
is located?  He says he is in Punjab.  [laughter]
I didn't say where exactly does it fall?
Punjab says.  I said what kind of place?  He says it is a very
nice place, brother.  You come sometime.  I said friend,
I will try.  He says one of your
relatives lives there.  I said I don't have
anyone living with me.  He says there must be someone.
Everyone has it in Kapurtala.
[laughter]
I said no, I don't have anyone living there.
Where should you ask at your home?  [laughter] I said
no, I don't want to ask like that.  Ok.   I
said no, it is no, at least someone has happened.   It happens to
everyone.  Guys
[sound of clearing throat] you guys probably forgot.
A man is going to die here.
[laughter]
He's been trying to say something for the last 15 minutes.  I am
not listening to anything.
Finally I said, brother, tell me what are you saying
?
My mother lives in Kapurla.  [Applause]
Then he died.  [laughter]
[sound of clearing throat] There's
no fun there.  Basically they do
n't have stories to tell.  As
I saw there, a couple was walking.  The boy
suddenly came forward.  Ok?  And he took out the ring.
He took out the ring and went to Nice.   He
says you mean the world to me.  Say you
marry me.  And the girl said yes.  Thousands of people started
clapping.  [laughter] Let me
tell you about Noida.
A couple was also moving in Noida.  [laughter] The
boy suddenly came forward.  He took out the ring.
Went to Nice.  I was just about to start proposing.
Beast Proposal Someone stole the ring and ran away.
[Applause]
That girl has run after him.  The boy
is sitting there.  [laughter]
You guys are lucky to be born in this country.
You will die here.  What a happy
thing this is, friend.  Like in India, people who are paying
attention to fitness, I think they are
big idiots.  Location is very
important.
[laughs] There's
no need to focus on fitness everywhere.  You live in Europe, there may be some
benefit there.  He was my friend and a gym
trainer.  He said, friend, your body is
your temple.  Take care of your body.  He was
shot in the temple.  [laughter] I could
n't even run away.  That first bullet
hit the leg.  [laughs] After hitting him he said, O
Dalbir, this is someone else.
Good fun brother.  I enjoy living in this country.  It
is a very nice country.  There is nothing there.
They don't behave
with each other there.  Don't talk.
I'm not pretending to be in a cab in Europe.
This really happened.  I sat in the cab and
he dropped me wherever I wanted to go.
[laughs] I did
n't talk about anything without it.  Didn't tell
how much land uncle has grabbed.
[sound of clearing throat][laughter] I didn't
tell you what was going on with me.  Nothing.
You can sit in the cab here.  You get a story.  While sitting
in my cab he says,
brother, do I drive or do I have a hobby?  I don't
need it.
I said I sit for the need.
[Applause] I don't have
any hobbies.
Please drop me wherever I want to go.
Whenever you sit in a cab, the cab driver should
not know that you are in a hurry to reach somewhere.  If
he finds out, he will immediately
stop at the CNG pump.  [laughter]
He shouldn't know.  I sat in the cab.
I said sir it is time for the flight.  Have to
reach quickly.  Said sir, I will move at the speed of a bullet.
After 5 minutes, it stopped at the CNG bomb.
[laughter]
I said, Sir, what pill is this?  Which
moved at a speed of 24 km per hour and then
suddenly stopped.  He is saying sir it will take 5 minutes.  There are
only 300 vehicles.
[laughter]
After one and a half hours our turn came.
Then he comes and says, Sir, get down from the car now.
I asked why?  So he says, Sir, I want to
fill CNG.  I said I'll grab the pipe.
[laughter]
What's wrong with me sitting down?
Sir, if the CNG explodes, we will die
[laughs]
So I got down from the cab, he also got down from the cab,
both of us stood on the car
like this [laughs] It will
explode only inside
[laughs]
We are safe outside.
Then he asks me [laughs]
what time is your flight?
I said, look she is going [laughs], she left,
reached, she got bored, she is gone [laughs]
so it is
best that we should be arrogant about this, but
we are there too [laughs], by the way, it is a
good thing, tell me
why are the Europeans so far behind us,
because they are moving away from religion, they have
shrunk a bit, there is no
such thing.  Religion is very
good.  Our country exists only because of religion.  Otherwise, who knows
where we would have been.
[Praise]
Religion Is Very Beautiful.  Religion is very
personal.  I am not going to make any fun of religion.
Religion is very beautiful.  All the
religions are equally beautiful.  One
is a little better.  The
rest [applause] The rest they are trying to catch
up.  Everything is good in its own place.  There
is no such problem.  Religion is
beautiful.  Your religion is like that of your father.
You get it as soon as you are born.
You don't ask him any questions.   You
accept it as it is and are
unable to hear anything against it.  Someone else's
religion is like his uncle.  Sam is just
like your father.  But you think he will
take over our house.  [laughter]
[applause] [encouraging voice]
[applause]
But you forget one thing: your father is also
someone's uncle.  This thought [laughs] is
not to be thought at all, it doesn't matter.  Religion is
beautiful.  Look,
I have read all the religions and I liked them all.
But there are things written in religion which are
not practical.  Good things have been written.
It is written how the world should be.
But what the world is like is not written.
As it is written in every religious book,
in the battle between truth and falsehood, truth always wins.
Where is truth winning?   Have
you ever seen truth win?
Truth never wins.  There should be a practical religion in
which it is written that in the battle between truth and falsehood,
victory is achieved.
Who owns Toyota Fortuner.  That's how he wins.
You see, he never loses.
By the way, if any MLA or MP is travelling in Alto
, slap him.  [laughter]
He won't be able to do anything.  But if
even a TCS employee cannot go below TCS,
then I am on the bench at TCS.
[laughter]
[appreciation]
Even if a TCS employee is in Fortune,
he will be respected, friend.  Such
practical things should be there in religion.
She is not available.  Like in the battle between truth and lies, the one who knows the
local
language will win.  [laughter]
Look, he's always winning.  Who will win in Bor
who knows Kannada.
Who will win in Mumbai who knows Marathi?
Who will win in Gurgaon who knows how to shoot?
[Applause]
A man shot in Gurgaon.
He asked why did you hit me?  So he says it was terrible.
[laughter]
How was the grimace?
After seeing him he said, oh this is my aunt's son.
[laughter]
Religion is beautiful.  I like religion.
I like religion.  Religious
[sound of clearing throat]
Praise people about their religion.  How unhappy
those people are.
Praise the scriptures they have.  How happy they are.   You will
tell someone that what is
written in your religion is a very good thing.  He said,
I was already saying it.  We are the best.  Come,
you also come this side.  [laughter] Come on, come on.   That
is a small procedure.  I am saying listen to me.
[Applause]
Listen to me.  After turning these two pages,
what is written is not a small problem, I
mean this thing.  Well
[sound of clearing throat] this one does
n't mean what it says.
It has context.
[sound of clearing throat] This is not what it says.
It has some other meaning.
We don't know that.  He knows that.  It has
context.  But what you are reading is
not its meaning.  This also has a good
meaning.  There is something else to it.  I said,
but there might be something more to what I liked.
[laughter]
Give me the sword for a minute, friend.
[applause] [encouraging voice]
And those atheists are nothing special either.
They also have nothing to say.   They come up with the
same four or five worn out sentences.  All these
atheists,
you must have always heard one phrase that well
[sound of clearing throat] this is your
scripture.  This is your book.   According to this,
whatever is written about your God, it exists
and you believe that it exists.
Here's the Spiderman book.  What does it mean
?  There's also Spiderman.  [laughter] Is that a
thing?  Is there any logic in this?  How
illogical is this.  There
can be no comparison.  How illogical because there is
Spiderman after all.
Spiderman
is alive in Spiderman Actually.  It's Spiderman.   There
is also Spiderman India.  Spiderman came to Gurgaon.
[laughter]
You wouldn't know.  Spiderman came to Gurgaon.
Those who don't
know Spiderman, he doesn't do such Rapido Uber.  He has his
own mood of transport.  He
throws webs.  [laughter]
So there was a crime going on somewhere.  He was going to save by
throwing nets.  A web was thrown and
crossed the building.  The second web was thrown and
crossed the building.
He threw the third net at the house of a Jat brother.
[laughter] He ran over the railing and stumbled.
And he was crossing it.  Did Jat Bhai
notice what was happening?  [laughter]
Jat Bhai saw the net hanging.  A guy is
crossing.  I am not lying.
[Laughter]
Jat Bhai pulled up Spiderman along with his web
like this.
[Praise]
Friends, there is no sound of ass getting torn.
[laughter]
But the explosion that happened in his backyard.  She got her
ass filled.  What is this happening?  He kept pulling with so much strength
[laughs].  The
cold came, I
pulled it up.  [laughter]
Are you waiting?  Spiderman said, waiting [laughter].
[laughter]
With great power.  [laughter]
Comes great responsibility
[appreciation]
Yes hands behind me
listen to me, you listen to me carefully
[laughter] Do you want PG or PG
double sharing triple sharing [laughter] with
food without food he cannot go from here
[laughter]
then he went back.  Look, religion is
beautiful.  I respect your religion.  Meaning,
one is the best and the rest are also almost there.  So
basically [laughs]
I read all the religions.  A thought came to me.
I want to share with you guys.
That thought was that there are many religions.
And the whole world is fighting among themselves in the name of religion.
If we just follow what is common in all religions,
how much better a place would the world become.
Every religion has many things in common.  Like it is
written in every religion that we should help the helpless.
When I read this and then
I read it in all the religions, I
decided that I will help the helpless.
Because it is written in every book.
If there is a God, then this is what God really wants.
I decided I would
help the destitute.  I just want to meet him somewhere.  [laughter]
Now I'm on the lookout.  I just hope I find him helpless somewhere.  I will
help you with my wisdom.   I just want to meet him
somewhere.  If you don't find it, I will make it.   I
convert myself.  I said I just want to find him
somewhere helpless.  Once I felt like helping a
blind person cross the road.  I ca
n't find the blind one.  [laughter]
Then there was a man standing there.
I put my fingers in his eyes like this.  Then like this here
organ [laughs]
then walk walk walk.  Helped me cross the road.  It was a
good feeling.  [Laughter]
Just think, you might think I made a man
blind.  But I also got my practice done.
[laughter]
Next time I'll get someone who's actually blind.
I know what to do.  It's a good feeling.  I
live in this divorce, I just want to meet you somewhere.  Let me
tell you a true story.
I was in a market in Delhi.  My
target for that day was not achieved.  I had to
help someone.
A man in front of me had a heart attack.
I am happy and I say yes.  [laughter] I'll help him.
When something bad happens to you
in this country, you feel that nothing worse can happen than this.
But it happens.  He must be thinking that nothing can be
worse than this.  I
reached there.  [laughter]
I arrived and he was in agony.  I did the same thing
you guys do.  I clicked his photo and
sent the chat to GPT.
I said it is shaking.  It is a heart attack.
Chat GPT asked me the opposite question whether
this was a heart attack or cardiac arrest
?  [laughter]
What do I know?
So I asked him.  I said brother, is
this a heart attack or cardiac arrest?   In the
middle of a heart attack he said son hey calm down friend
[laughs] calm
down brother you can't abuse like this you
relax relax I said to Chat GBT
again I tell you the treatment for both of them tell me the treatment for
heart attack tell me the treatment for cardiac race
then Chat GBT said if you are having a heart attack
then there is a medicine called Ecospin it is a blood thinner give it to you the blood will become thin and the
heart attack will stop
I said ok if you are having cardiac race then
what to do he said give CPR I
said what is CPR you send me the video
[laughs] of CPR
two middle aged men
[laughs]
licking each other's mouth.
One of the middle-aged men was very
sexy.  A bald, fat madman, both of them were
wearing white clothes.  And there were also frameless glasses.
Both were also from Gujarat.  So they
[applause]
[applause] are
licking each other like this.
So after watching that video I decided
that it was a heart attack.
[laughs]
I'm not licking his face.
So I went to the medical store to buy Ecospin medicine.
When I came back, friends,
I told you one thing right now that
something bad happens to you.  You think nothing can get
worse than this.  It happens.  When
I came back he was still having heart attacks.
But in the middle of the heart attack,
he was also bitten by a dog.
This doesn't happen anywhere else.  We do it.
[laughter] The beach is hard.  That dog is
not the one that bites and runs away.  That's what a dog is
[laughs]
I clicked a photo and sent it to Chat Gibbity.
How the dog has also bitten me.  Chat
Gibiti said we won't be able to do it.  Please forgive me.
I kicked the dog and chased it away.  See
whenever you hit a dog in this country you know what happens you know what happens a
woman suddenly appears
[laughs]
out of nowhere
I feel these women hide ke baithe rehti
hai divider pe ki atyachaan ho main pukka ho jaan as soon as I
hit her she appears you must have seen
those women wearing sports shoes under salwar kameez
[laughs]
[applause] have
short hair.  There is nasal tone.
As soon as I came, I could see your values.  Are
n't you ashamed?  You kicked a mute
animal.  Are you ashamed?
I said, Ma'am, that dog had bitten brother.  There is only
one answer to these.
He must have provoked it first.   The
dog will provoke a heart attack.  [laughter] Must have
provoked me.  That man who had a heart attack
told me, the woman and the dog all three of us to go
down.  You can't behave rudely like this.
[laughter]
Then I remembered I have a car.
Then I lifted him with someone's help.
Lay him down on the back seat.  Now I am
taking him to the hospital.  So I'm
trying to go to the hospital.  There is another
car moving in front of me.  There were five
boys in it and they were drinking alcohol.  how know?
He was out of the window.  And he had a
bottle of liquor in his hand.  One was even out of the sunroof.
So he was drinking.  And it wo
n't let me go further.  He was driving the car like this.
Like I [sound of clearing throat]
try to come here, come here, try to come here
, come here.  Then I saw there were
police barricades.  I thought he would get caught
now.  I was very happy.  As soon as the barricades
came, the policeman extended his hand to stop them.
Not making this up.
Gave a high-five to the policeman
and ran away.  [laughter]
And I started crossing.  Stopped me.
[laughter] Said roll down the window.  I did.
He says blow on it.  I said
why?  He says he wants to check whether you have consumed alcohol
?  I said, "
You didn't check the car that went before me. He
says he was definitely drunk."
[Laughter]
[Prashant]
You're not sure. I said, "Sir, understand what
I'm saying. There's a heart attack patient behind.
He's having a heart attack. Do you know
what the policeman told me? He
told me he was having a heart attack. I said, '
Yes, you did.' [Laughter]
I put my hand over his mouth and shook his heart.
[Laughter] He
says this is illegal. I said, 'Listen to me.
Please listen to me. It's a natural
heart attack.' Then another policeman came. He
said, 'How do you know it's a heart attack? It could be a
cardiac arrest.' I
said, 'Yes, it could be.' He asked, '
What do you do then?' I said, 'Give CPR.' He said, 'Give it.' I said, 'I ca
n't.' He said, 'I'll give it.' I said, 'Give it.' He
asked, 'How do you do it?'
I showed him the video.
After watching the video, he said, 'No, it's a heart
attack. It's a
heart attack.' [Prashant]
So when I got to the hospital, I found out this
man had gas. [laughter]
I dropped him back where I picked him up.
[laughter]
Exactly at the same point. [applause]
He said, drop me home. I said, it does
n't work like that. You had gas. [laughter]
You overacted so much. Three days later, I was
reading the newspaper. I saw that man's photo.
I was so happy. I
told my wife, look, I saved his life.
She said, "You should read what's written."
I read the newspaper. Friends, that man
died of rabies.
[music]